http://www.downtime-metal.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@www.downtime-metal.com.
At Downtime Metal, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Downtime Metal and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, Downtime Metal makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Downtime Metal does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Downtime Metal send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
Downtime Metal has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Downtime Metal privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers respective websites.
Search for:
Songs Workshop Software Programs Utilised for Insurance Services
Music Studio Solutions Designed for Insurance Firms
The Need for Short term Insurance Services for Music Studios
Test
Links Page
Private Studio Management Skills Required by Construction Recruiters
Software Innovations that Facilitate Construction Services
Music Applications for Building Contractors
Software that Enables Better Building Marketing Services
How to Leverage Music Technology When Selling Building Products
Bedding Companies That Support Home Music Studios
The Advantages Of Having A Bed Specialist During A Home Music Studio Construction
Bedding Specialists And Their Role In Music Studios
Bedding Infrastructure Installed In Music Studios
Advantages of Engaging a Property Agent for Music Software Owners
The Importance Of Rental Property Agents To Music Software Administrators
Marketing Firms Conducting Consulting Services For Music Studios
Downtime Studios Analyses Media Buying Agencies in Johannesburg
